<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Minimal</title>
    <link>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Minimal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 16:53:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ts-xie.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Battle Between Angular and Vue</title>
      <link>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/the-battle-between-angular-and-vue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 16:53:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/the-battle-between-angular-and-vue/</guid>
      <description>Personally, I don’t mind to switch frameworks because each one has its pros and cons, and I always like to try new techs and learn from it. I’ve used jQuery, Backbone, Angular1, Vue.js so far, and really you can see how frontend evolve so fast and those frameworks and concepts make frontend development much easier than before.
Angular is a great framework and introduced two day data binding, dependency injection, modularization etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding D3 Data Join</title>
      <link>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/understanding-d3-data-join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 15:52:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/understanding-d3-data-join/</guid>
      <description>Intro D3.js has simple but powerful APIs that allows us to do data driven development, creating and modifying DOM elements based on data change. All thanks to the design of D3 selection and data join. Here I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how D3 data join works behind the scenes. Also check out Thinking with Joins, a great explanation from Mike Bostock, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet.
Selection A selection is groups of selected elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Is the Best Developer I Have Ever Known</title>
      <link>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/tom-is-the-best-developer-i-have-ever-known/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 22:30:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/tom-is-the-best-developer-i-have-ever-known/</guid>
      <description>Tom started programming since he&amp;rsquo;s 14 and he loves it ever since.
Tom knows things. He knows things in and out. He likes to quote from Richard Feynman &amp;ldquo;What I cannot create, I do not understand&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s really hard to ask a question that he cannot answer, if that happens, he always dig into it and find the answer eventually.
Tom knows a lot of things. He always stay curious about the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best at Clash Royale</title>
      <link>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/best-at-clash-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 12:10:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ts-xie.github.io/post/best-at-clash-royale/</guid>
      <description>Intro I have been playing this game for about two years, and I really LOVE this game! In this blog, I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about few things that I feel is important to be a good player. Those are only from my experience and understanding of this game.
Basics 1. Understanding the rules of the game First thing to know is understand the game. For example, what is the win condition? what is elixir?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>